{"test_questions": [[{"question": "Which statement below best describes a Karnaugh map?", "opta": "It is simply a rearranged truth table.", "optb": "The Karnaugh map eliminates the need for using NAND and NOR gates.", "optc": "Variable complements can be eliminated by using Karnaugh maps.", "optd": "A Karnaugh map can be used to replace Boolean rules.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the examples below expresses the commutative law of multiplication?", "opta": "A + B = B + A", "optb": "A \u0095 B = B + A", "optc": "A \u0095 (B \u0095 C) = (A \u0095 B) \u0095 C", "optd": "A \u0095 B = B \u0095 A", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The Boolean expression  is logically equivalent to what single gate?", "opta": "NAND", "optb": "NOR", "optc": "AND", "optd": "OR", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The observation that a bubbled input OR gate is interchangeable with a bubbled output AND gate is referred to as:", "opta": "a Karnaugh map", "optb": "DeMorgan's second theorem", "optc": "the commutative law of addition", "optd": "the associative law of multiplication", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The systematic reduction of logic circuits is accomplished by:", "opta": "symbolic reduction", "optb": "TTL logic", "optc": "using Boolean algebra", "optd": "using a truth table", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Logically, the output of a NOR gate would have the same Boolean expression as a(n):", "opta": "NAND gate immediately followed by an INVERTER", "optb": "OR gate immediately followed by an INVERTER", "optc": "AND gate immediately followed by an INVERTER", "optd": "NOR gate immediately followed by an INVERTER", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the examples below expresses the distributive law of Boolean algebra?", "opta": "A \u0095 (B \u0095 C) = (A \u0095 B) + C", "optb": "A + (B + C) = (A \u0095 B) + (A \u0095 C)", "optc": "A \u0095 (B + C) = (A \u0095 B) + (A \u0095 C)", "optd": "(A + B) + C = A + (B + C)", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which output expression might indicate a product-of-sums circuit construction?", "opta": "", "optb": "", "optc": "", "optd": "", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "One of  DeMorgan's theorems states that . Simply stated, this means that logically there is no difference between:", "opta": "a NAND gate and an AND gate with a bubbled output", "optb": "a NOR gate and an AND gate with a bubbled output", "optc": "a NOR gate and a NAND gate with a bubbled output", "optd": "a NAND gate and an OR gate with a bubbled output", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The commutative law of addition and multiplication indicates that:", "opta": "the way we OR or AND two variables is unimportant because the result is the same", "optb": "we can group variables in an AND or in an OR any way we want", "optc": "an expression can be expanded by multiplying term by term just the same as in ordinary algebra", "optd": "the factoring of Boolean expressions requires the multiplication of product terms that contain like variables", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following expressions is in the sum-of-products (SOP) form?", "opta": "Y = (A + B)(C + D)", "optb": "Y = AB(CD)", "optc": "", "optd": "", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}